<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<!--===== Predator =====-->

	<Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef ParentName="VehicleBaseBuildable">
		<defName>GW_Predator_Blueprint</defName>
		<label>Predator Tank</label>
		<description>In the grim theater of GrimWorld 40,000, the Predator Tank emerges as a relentless war machine. With its iconic design and battle-hardened presence, this armored behemoth symbolizes the indomitable might of the Imperium in the tumultuous 41st millennium.\n\nClad in scarred plating and adorned with Imperial symbols, the Predator Tank bears witness to countless engagements, reflecting its unwavering commitment to the Emperor's cause. Its utilitarian yet imposing aesthetic speaks to the harsh realities of warfare in a galaxy consumed by darkness.\n\nFeaturing a lethal array of weaponry, the Predator Tank is a symbol of devastating firepower on the battlefield. Whether engaging armored targets or sweeping through infantry lines, it stands as a stalwart defender of the Imperium's dominion.\n\nAs it rumbles across the war-torn landscape, the Predator Tank embodies the relentless spirit of the Imperium, a bulwark against the encroaching shadows and a testament to the unyielding strength of GrimWorld 40,000. \n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Driver x1, Gunner x1, Passenger x2\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</description>
		<designationCategory>GrimworldCategory</designationCategory>
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Vehicles/Predator/Predator</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Multi</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>(4, 5)</drawSize>
		</graphicData>
		<statBases>
			<MaxHitPoints>500</MaxHitPoints>
			<WorkToBuild>17500</WorkToBuild>
			<Flammability>0.05</Flammability>
		</statBases>
		<size>(4, 5)</size>
		<researchPrerequisites>
			<li>GW_ImperialLandMilitaryHeavyVehicleResearch</li>
		</researchPrerequisites>
		<costList>
			<Steel>650</Steel>
			<HP_Ceramite>300</HP_Ceramite>
			<HP_Adamantium>15</HP_Adamantium>
			<GW_VehicleCannon>1</GW_VehicleCannon>
			<GW_VehicleEngine>1</GW_VehicleEngine>
			<GW_VehicleExhaust>2</GW_VehicleExhaust>
			<GW_VehicleSideTurret>2</GW_VehicleSideTurret>
			<GW_VehicleSuspension>14</GW_VehicleSuspension>
			<GW_VehicleTracks>2</GW_VehicleTracks>
			<GW_VehicleWheel>22</GW_VehicleWheel>
			<ComponentIndustrial>20</ComponentIndustrial>
		</costList>
		<soundImpactDefault>BulletImpact_Metal</soundImpactDefault>
		<thingToSpawn>GW_Predator</thingToSpawn>
		<constructionSkillPrerequisite>8</constructionSkillPrerequisite>
	</Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef>
</Defs>