<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>

<Defs>
	<Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef ParentName="VehicleBaseBuildable">
		<defName>GW_DropPod_Blueprint</defName>
		<label>Drop Pod</label>
		<description>In the grim expanse of GrimWorld 40,000, the Astartes Drop Pod stands as an epitome of rapid deployment and shock assault. Crafted with a utilitarian yet imposing design, this angular pod reflects the brutal efficiency of the Space Marines.\n\nClad in battle-scarred plating, adorned with chapter-specific iconography, the Drop Pod exudes the stark aesthetic of the 41st millennium. Its surface bears the marks of countless atmospheric entries, a testament to the relentless engagements it endures in service to the Emperor.\n\nHinged doors, bearing the weight of the chapter's honor, guard the pod's interior. Upon deployment, they swing open with a purpose, revealing the heart of the assault. The Drop Pod is not merely a vessel; it is a harbinger of war, carrying within its metallic confines the Emperor's wrath.\n\nInternally, the pod features a mix of arcane machinery and battle-ready stasis racks for Astartes weaponry. Cables and conduits snake through the compartment, connecting to the dormant war gear that awaits activation upon the pod's descent.\n\nUpon touchdown, the Drop Pod disgorges its cargo, delivering Space Marines directly into the heart of the battle. The resounding impact echoes the uncompromising nature of the Astartes, symbolizing the Imperium's relentless pushback against the encroaching darkness in GrimWorld 40,000. \n\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Crew:&lt;/color&gt; Operator x1, Passenger x3\n&lt;color=#bb8f04&gt;Fuel type:&lt;/color&gt; Chemfuel</description>
		<designationCategory>GrimworldCategory</designationCategory>
		
		<graphicData>
			<texPath>Things/Vehicles/DropPod/DropPod</texPath>
			<graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
			<drawSize>(8, 8)</drawSize>
			<drawRotated>false</drawRotated>
		</graphicData>
		
	<rotatable>false</rotatable>
	<statBases>
		<MaxHitPoints>500</MaxHitPoints>
		<WorkToBuild>12000</WorkToBuild>
		<Flammability>0</Flammability>
	</statBases>
	
	<size>(7, 7)</size>
	
	<researchPrerequisites>
		<li>GW_ImperialAirVehicleResearch</li>
	</researchPrerequisites>
	
	<costList>
			<Steel>750</Steel>
			<HP_Ceramite>375</HP_Ceramite>
			<HP_Adamantium>25</HP_Adamantium>
			<GW_JetEngine>1</GW_JetEngine>
			<GW_VehicleExhaust>5</GW_VehicleExhaust>
			<ComponentIndustrial>26</ComponentIndustrial>
		</costList>
		
		<soundImpactDefault>BulletImpact_Metal</soundImpactDefault>
		<thingToSpawn>GW_DropPod</thingToSpawn>
		
		<constructionSkillPrerequisite>6</constructionSkillPrerequisite>
	</Vehicles.VehicleBuildDef>
</Defs>
